Zunaid Ali Hashmi

Aspiring Web Developer | Problem Solver | Quick Learner

zunaidalihashmi0786@gmail.com +91-8416914173

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sa yed-junaid-ali-b53143159/

JOB DESCRIPTION

Enthusiastic and dedicated Junior Full Stack Developer with 1 years of experience in web application development. Eager to contribute my skills and passion for coding to a dynamic team, focused on building efficient and user-friendly digital solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Axes Geeks pvt ltd, Noida, Uttar Pradesh — Internship Sept 2021 - June 2022

In my very first internship, I had the chance of working with Python and Django to develop a CRM system management level app. And as it's one of the most popular web development frameworks, I decided to share my thoughts on it.

Virtus IT pvt ltd, Hyderabad — Full Stack Developer

July 2022 - Present 2023

As a junior team member, I actively participated in tasks assigned by senior developers. My responsibilities encompassed crafting essential website sections and assisting in the development of Javascript and Asp .Net MVC , C# Functionality , with a focus on user validation data getting, sign-up, and email services. Guided by senior colleagues, I contributed to building foundational skills.

EDUCATION

Rgpv University, Bhopal — B.tech

June 2017 - June 2021

PROJECTS

Ecommerce Website Played a role in enhancing the frontend user experience by utilizing Asp .NET, ReactJS,, HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap. Additionally, search, pagination, and essential product management functionalities, aiming to enhance the website's accessibility and overall performance.

SKILLS

JavaScript

JQuery

Ajax

Asp .Net MVC

C#

ReactJs

Python

Django

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Git

AWARDS

Python Guide Certification | Naresh IT | June 2018

Volleyball State Level | 2017

LANGUAGES

English (conversational)

Hindi (native)

https://www.smsaexpress.com/node/18

https://www.store2door.com/public/en/Home.aspx